







1

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Summary

Jump to Section

Last Active: 20-Jan-21

More than 18 years of professional experience in positions as System Administrator & Service Engineer. Involved in PC assembling, maintenance & trouble shooting. Have good experience in various types of printer repairing. Involved in Network configurations, maintenance & support Currently working as System Administrator at Neo Industries. Worked in close interaction with clients.

Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Work Experience

Neo Industries as System Administrator Jan 2012 to Till Date

Seeking a professional position as system administrator requiring advanced technical knowledge and looking forward to work in a competitive environment that effectively utilizes my analytical, interpersonal, leadership and organizational skills to conceive and achieve solutions. The solutions which help the organization in not only meeting its targets, but also allowing it to grow, thereby enhancing my own skills as an individual and as a key player in the organization's development.

Carnation Auto India as System Administrator Aug 2008 to Dec 2011

system administrator

Neo Industries as system support executive Jan 2005 to Jul 2008

system administrator

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: microsoft certified professional (server adminidtration), Correspondence/Distance Learning from sohobit university in 2005

^ Back to Top

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
Windows '98, Windows NT, Windows XP	
Windows 7,10, windows 2000 server	
MS OFFICE	

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
ENGLISH				
HINDI				
BENGALI				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: **General**Physically Challenged: **No**

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.